好的,  站在这儿
All right,stand here.
你刚好够高
You're just tall enough.
我--我不觉得
I--i don't--I don't think I am.
只不过是转圈
It just goes around.
没什么可怕的, 对不?
There's nothingto be scared of, all right?
谁说我害怕了
I didn't say I was scared.
很好玩的,来吧
It'll be fun.,Come on.
我小时候最爱玩这个了
When I was a kid, this wasmy favorite thing ever.
我不喜欢坐旋转飞车
I don't like rides.
没事, 没事,我只是以为这会很好玩
All right, all right.,I just--I thoughtit'd be fun.
我不该逼你玩这个
I shouldn't bemaking you do this.
呃... 回家吧,我们可以回家玩
Uh...let's go home.,We can have fun at home.
不, 爸爸, 等等
No, daddy, wait.
旋转飞车看上去好像很好玩
The ride doeslook like fun.
哦, 真是太棒了!
Oh, this is awesome!
alice, 你没事吧?
alice, are you all right?
亲爱的, 你没事吧?
Honey, you all right?
alice!,alice  你怎么了?
Alice!,Alice, are you okay?
-=豪斯医生=-,S03E09 "Finding Judas"
House,Season 3 Episode 09
- 什么事也没有,- 一定有事发生了
- nothing happened.,- something happened.
- 只不过是小孩子玩的旋转飞车,- 她不喜欢玩旋转飞车
- It was a little kiddie ride.,- She hates those rides.
我不明白为什么你总是--
I don't understand whyyou insist on making--
好了, 我很感谢你们回答得这样详细
okay, I appreciatethe fullness,of your answers,
我要知道的是,她是否得过任何腹部疾病
but I just wanted to know if she had,any historyof abdominal problems.
- 没有,- 没有
- No.,- No.
入院纪录上写着没有家族病史--
The admitting doctornoted,no family history of--
我有个姑妈有克朗氏症,(慢性肉芽肿性炎症)
I have an aunt withcrohn's disease.
- 你没说吗?,- 我忘了那个叫什么病
- You didn'tmention that?,- I--I forgotwhat it was called.
你姑妈全身都是病
Your aunt has got,a million things wrong with her.
如果你能集中哪怕是五分钟的注意力--
If you paid attentionfor five minutes--
我不认为这是克朗氏症,她没有任何这方面的症状
I doubt it's crohn'S.,She has none ofthe other systems.
你只跟她单独待了8 个小时,而她就落了个住院的结果
You're alone with herfor eight hours,,she ends upin the hospital.
Hartmann夫人,能不能把重点放在回答问题上
I'm wondering if wecan focus on,answering the questions,mrs. Hartmann.
我不是Hartmann夫人,我们离婚了
I'm not mrs. Hartmann.,We're divorced.
我猜也是
I suspected.
您慷慨大方的名声,让我想到要找您谈谈
And your pasgenerositymade me think of you.
我们还有50万元资金的缺口
We're half a milliondollars from our goal.
当然, 这对您的基金会来说,也是个冠名的机会
Of course, this isa naming opportunityfor your foundation.
有-- 有什么问题吗?
Is--is there a problem?
你脸上有东西
There's somethingon your face.
那个是...呃
It's, uh--ahem.
不好意思
Excuse me.
- 哦!,- 哦, 天那
- Oh!,- Oh, god.
我还真希望那是狙击手,那样至少那疯子跟我的医院无关
I'm sitting in therehoping it's a sniper,because at thenthe sociopathisn't my employee.
我靠这个小东西在医院赢得,"体内取出怪异物体"比赛第二名
This baby won mesecond placein the clinic's weekly,"weirdest thing pulled outof an orifice" contest.
我只差一点就为肿瘤科,搞到一所新实验室了
I am this close to putting,a new lab in oncology.
猜猜看有什么大事?
You do not want to knowwhat came in first.
- House,- 跟“fucchini”压韵
- House.,- Rhymes with "fucchini".
把他的药给我
Give me his pills.
- 我的处方呢?,- 不能再给你开流动处方了
- Where's my prescription?,- No more free floatingprescriptions.
普林斯顿警局已经逼得,Wilson关门大吉
Princeton pd has already,forced wilson to shut down.
一个警察看着不爽,wilson就得关门
A cop says boo,wilson shuts down.
这里的每个医生都变得小心翼翼
Every doctor in this place is afraid to,make a movewithout covering his ass.
你不觉得你怪错人了吗?
Do you think maybe you're,shouting at the wrong person?
Tritter就是想报复我,他根本就不在乎
Tritter's obviouslyout to get me.,He doesn't care--
- 你伪造了处方,- 没证据
- your forged prescriptions!,- Allegedly.
你的麻烦已经成了我的麻烦
Your pain hasbecome my pain.
从现在起, 你得在正常的次数内,服用正常的量
From now on you get reasonable,dosesat reasonable times.
可我一疼起来就没个正常
But I hurt inan unreasonable way.
- 那就去翻翻你的秘密存货,- 被Tritter拿走了
- Then dip intoyour secret stash.,- Tritter took it.
- 那就去翻翻你的绝密存货,- 已经用完了
- Then move ontoyour secret secret stash.,- I ran out.
那就去翻翻你的顶级绝密存货
Then move onto your,secret secret secret stash.
父母声称她没有服用过任何药物
Parents sayshe's not on any med.
如果不是由药物导致的胰腺炎,而她又没有别的病
If the pancreatitiswasn't set off,by drugs,and she hasn't been sick,
那就只能是外伤或者是,某种组织缺陷引起的, 让她去照照CT
that leaves traumaor some kind,of structural defect.Put up the ct.
- 那块暗点是怎么回事?,- 阴影  看上去相当正常
- what's that density there?,- Shadow.Looks normal to me.
- 我们咨询了--,- 不好意思
- We got a referral from--,- excuse me.
居然把药藏在狼疮病理学课本里
You stash your drugs,in a lupus textbook.
反正从来不是狼疮
It's never lupus.
什么人得了胆结石,干嘛要搞得那么隆重啊?
Who's got gallstones,,and why do we care?
- 胆结石?,- 胆管扩张了
- Gallstones?,- Biliary duct is dilated.
可能是结石造成的,一定已经导致严重的胰腺炎了
Probably from a stonelodged in it.,Must've caused a nasty caseof pancreatitis.
她只有六岁,六岁的小孩不会得胆结石
she's six.,Six-year-olds don'tget gallstones.
所以她得的不是胰腺炎
So she didn't havepancreatitis.
你的意思是她长了颗隐形胆结石
Your theory isan invisible gallstone?
他的正确推断是胰腺炎
His theory correctlypredicted pancreatitis.
拍马屁也要等他把话讲完好不好
You might want to waituntil he actually tells us,his theory before you startkissing his theory's ass.
我的意思是...,胆结石消失了
my theory is...,vanishing gallstone.
原先有过, 后来排出去了,这玩艺要有就是一堆
She had it,and it passed.,Those thingstravel in packs.
其余的胆结石可能藏在她的胆囊里,让她做个B超
The rest of them are probablyhiding out,in her gall bladder.Do an ultrasound.
如果我正确, 就得切除掉胆囊,对那些结石作分析
If I'm right,we'll take out the organ,so we can analyzethe stones.
我没拍他的马屁
I wasn't kissing his ass.
我怎么看着就象
it must've just looked,that way from our angle.
- house一弯腰, 你马上就下跪,- 他说中了胰腺炎
- You on your knees,house bending over.,- He predictedthe pancreatitis.
- 这都是他老爸的错,- 我老爸是个混蛋
- It's his dad's fault.,- My dad was an ass.
可你却一直对他言听计从,作为回报, 你也得到了自己想要的一切
But you did everythinghe wanted you to,,and in return you goteverything you wanted.
就是这么简单?
Yeah, it's that simple.
这一套很管用, 老爸给他安排轻松的工作,给钱让他过轻松的生活
The strategy worked.,Dad got him a cushy job.Paid for his cushy life.
然后把我的名字从遗嘱里轻松地划掉
Cut me outof hisushy will.
我早说了, 那是他的本性,可怜的家伙生来就是要拍马屁的
I told you.It's just his nature.,Poor guy's hardwiredto kiss ass.
House说得对,是胆结石
House was right.,Gallstones.
那么小的孩子也会得胆结石
I didn't know a kidcould get gallstones.
确实很罕见, 所以我们要,弄清楚是什么引起的
It's unusual.That's why we need,to see what's causing it.
我们必须切除alice的胆囊,分析这些结石
We'd like to removealice's gallbladder,and analyze the stones.
- 没问题,- 不行
- Sure.,- No.
- 就因为我说了“没问题”?,- 我的决定与你无关
- Just 'causeI said sure?,- I am capableof my own thoughts.
这只是个小手术,胆囊对人体不是很重要
It's a simple procedure.,The gallbladderisn't essential--
edie  医生认为该怎么做,我们就该让他们做
if the doctor thinkswe should do it,,we should do it, edie.
切除掉我们孩子的器官之前,是不是该征询一下其他医生的意见?
You think maybe we shouldget a second opinion,before we start removingour child's organs?
你可真能浪费纳税人的钱
That's an effective useof taxpayers' money.
- 这星期我休息,- 我猜你没有家
- I'm actually offthis week.,- I'm guessing you don'thave a family.
大多数人都疲于应付生活中的各种问题,所以没工夫去斤斤计较个人恩怨
Most people have enoughgoing on in their lives,that they don't have topersonalize every slight.
这不是个人恩怨,不再是了
This isn't personal.,Not anymore.
我的肿瘤科主任被迫关门
My head of oncologyhad to shut down.
所有的员工都因此变得谨小慎微,不敢越雷池半步
My entire staff areafraid to make a move,without coveringtheir ass.
我想你怪错人了
I think you're angryat the wrong person.
你认为Wilson医生活该被冻结财产?
You think dr. Wilson deserved,to have his assets seized?
- 职业毁于一旦?,- 不是
- His entire practice ruined?,- No.
你只是根本不在乎?
So you just don't care?
我就是靠这个来达到目的
This is how I getwhat I want.
我给别人施压
I put pressure on people.
就算wilson不肯就范,你已经开始着急了
And if it doesn't workon wilson,it'll work on you.
你惩罚的是无辜的人
You punish the innocent.
你们当中没有人是无辜的,没有一个
None of youare innocent.,Not one of you.
你们谁也不肯告诉我,关于House医生的真相
Not one of you has told methe truth.,About dr. House.
那些药帮助他对付疼痛
The pills allow himto cope with the pain.
不,  那些药丸扭曲了现实,他是个瘾君子
No, the pillsdistort reality.,He is an addict.
- 他又没去打劫烈酒商店或者--,- 没错, 可他是个医生
- He's not out robbinga liquor store or--,- no, he's treating people.
在他弄出人命之前,得想点别的办法解决这个问题
He needs to finda different way to cope,before he kills somebody.
说不定他已经弄出人命了
If he hasn'tdone that already.
就算你说得对,他也只不是有病而已
If you're right,he has a medical problem.
这应该由医生来解决,而不是--
It should be dealt withby doctors, not by--
医生们根本就没想要去解决问题,他们只会掩盖真相
well, it's not beingdealt with by doctors.,Doctors arecovering it up.
刑罚体系存在的目的是,当其它一切都失效, 守住最后一道防线
The whole point ofthe criminal justice system,is to make things rightwhen everything else fails.
我不是要打击你
With all due respect...
你已经管不住了
you have failed.
对不起, 不知道原来你们,都在盼着自己的孩子死掉
Sorry.,Didn't know you wantedyour kid dead.
不过, 再多花上几千快钱,我还是能帮你们达成心愿
Although, for a couple of g's,I could still make it happen.
你是什么人?
Who the hell are you?
陌生人一个, 只是比你们这做父母的,更关心孩子的生死
I am complete strangerwho apparently cares,more aboutwhether your kid diesthan you do.
- 你是House医生,- 你见过我的精彩演出了
- You're dr. House.,- You've seen my stage show.
她只是得了胰腺炎,没有生命危险
She's not dying.,She has pancreatitis.
治好以后,我就带她回家
Once you've treated that,I'm taking her home.
然后呢? 烧艾草驱邪?,我希望你能做这个手术
and do what, burn sage?,I want you to dothe surgery.
我父亲就得过胆结石,结石对人体完全无害
My father had gallstones.,They were totally harmless.
Alice有过一回, 可已经排出去了,在我们看来, 她已经没事了
Alice had one bad one,but it passed.,For all we knowthis is over.
可在我们看来,  她还没有康复,可能还会发作
And for all we know she could,get sick again tomorrow.
那我就带她看儿科医生,她只有六岁, Rob
Then I'll take her toher pediatrician.,She's six, rob.
她不该做没必要的手术
She shouldn't haveunnecessary surgery.
她也不该有个白痴妈妈,不过这有什么办法呢?
Or a moron for a mom,,but what can you do?
你只是她的医生,而我是她的妈妈
You're the doctor.,I'm the mother.
我比你大,接受现实吧
I outrank you.,Live with iT.
我读过相关资料了,你们有15分钟时间
I've read the file.,You've got 15 minutes.
哥白尼就是被这种人杀死的
It's like people like this,who killed copernicus.
- 是伽利略,- 都一样
- Galileo.,- Either way.
他们只是把伽利略关起来
And they justlocked galileo up.
他们扼杀了他的精神,没人喜欢爱臭显的家伙
They killed his spirit.,Nobody likes a showoff.
好在alice hartmann有个讲理的父亲
Luckily, alice hartmannhas a dad,who's willingto see reason.
你所谓的讲理就是指对你要俯首帖耳
Reason as defined byslavishly deferring to you.
是对他们的医生
Their doctor.
法官大人, 我还没机会咨询过我的律师
Your honor, I've hadno opportunity,to consult my attorney.
已经没时间了
There's noime.
- 我只想询问一下别的医生要不要--,- 没时间了
- All I want is a secondopinion before--,- no time!
你是说如果我不批准做这个手术,那孩子就会死, 对吧
Your testimony istheir child will die,if I don't grantthis motion right now.
- 我得说真话吗?,- 是的
- Am I under oath?,- Let's say yes.
我的意思是 如果你不马上批准这个手术,那孩子就有可能会死
My testimony is thatthis child might die,if you don't grantthis motion right now.
确实没时间去咨询别的医生
Literally no timefor a second opinion.
别的医生也不会比我更好
Wouldn't be as goodas the first opinion.
Cuddy 医生, 你的观点如何?
Dr. Cuddy,what do you think?
她的观点无足轻重,她又不是这领域的专家
She's not a specialistin this area.,Her opinion is worthless.
Cuddy医生, 你觉得House医生这人怎样?,是不是象我想的那样--是个大混蛋
Dr. Cuddy, what doyou think of dr. House?,Is he as big a jerkas I think he is?
比你想的更混,可他很清楚自己在说什么
Bigger.,But he knows whathe's talking about.
- 有什么事吗,- 她伤口缝线的地方不舒服
- Got a page.,- She's complainingabout her stitches.
护士说了那很正常
Nurse just saidthat's completely normal.
- 你拿到胆结石测试结果了吗?,- 马上就可以拿到
- Did you get the test resultsfor the gallstones?,- Any minute now.
说什么没有时间咨询别的医生,可这测试结果要等那么--
No time for a second opinion,but the test takes--
我的皮肤好疼
my skin hurts.
我明白自己没权要求你这么做,可你能不能瞧瞧这是怎么回事?
I know I no longerhave the right to demand it,,but could you pleasetake a look?
没问题
Sure.
她火气正大, 巴不得点出问题
She's pissed, now she's just,looking for things to go wrong.
说得没错, 我是很无耻,我希望她死, 这样就可以证明我是对的
You're right,I'm so petty,I hope she dies so itvindicates my opinion.
我不是这个意思, 亲爱的,妈咪是在说反话
I didn't mean that, sweetie.,Mommy was being sarcastic.
她还那么小,怎么知道什么是反话
she's a few years away from,grasping sarcasm,don't you think?
嗨
Guys.
我已经把号码给了你
I already gave youthat number.
一个简单的外科手术,就把小女孩变成了"英国病人"*
Simple surgical procedureturns a little girl,into the english patient.What gives?
也许是对手术中使用的某种药物过敏
Must be allergicto something,we used in the surgery.
这是我的办公室,该由我说话
This is my office.,I'm talking.
这些家伙都是我的手下
There are people herewho work for me.
却没一个人在听我说话,这到底是怎么回事
They're not listening.,Explain this to me.
Tritter 冻结了我的账户
Tritter froze my account.
他们在查别人的,我还在等着律师
They're checking theirs.,I'm on hold with a lawyer.
找wilson的律师, 他会给你解释,为什么你被整治了
Call wilson's lawyer.He'll tell you exactly,howand why you're screwed.
- 这孩子没有过敏史,- 你得去跟tritter谈谈
- This kid has no historyof allergies.,- You've gotta talk to tritter.
得把这事给摆平
You gotta make this go away.
是啊, 了不起的计划,还真以为那家伙会跟你讲道理
yeah, great plan.,The man's obviouslyopen to reason.
这么吧,我们不如就坐着干等
Well, here's the plan.,We do nothing.
把诊断病人的时间全浪费掉好了
We wile away the time diagnosing the patient.
结石是钙质的胆红素状石粒
The stones were calcium,bilirubinante, pigment stones.
成因很难判定
Which are non-conclusive.
伴随有低烧和轻度贫血的症状
Kid presented with,low-gradefever, mild anemia.
结石再加上这样的症状,表明是受到了细菌感染
That plus the stones indicate,bacterial infection.
细菌感染不会引起泡状皮疹
Bacterial infections don't,cause a vesicular rash.
坐着干等不是办法,实在没办法了才这么做
And doing nothingis not a plan.,It's specificallya lack of a plan.
我们切开她的肚子,坏家伙逃了出来
We cut into her belly.,Bad boys escape.
它们倾巢而出,四处攻城掠地 然后...
They swarm over, colonize the wounds,and...
咔砰!,皮疹就这么给整出来了
ka-plow!,Vesicular rash.
不管可能她有没有过敏史,很有可能还是过敏引起的
allergic reaction is 100% more likely,with or without a history.
低烧和贫血可能是胰腺炎的症状
Fever and anemia could've,been symptoms of pancreatitis.
喂?
Hello?
谢谢你的帮助
Thank you for your help.
- 他们冻结了我的账户,- 谢谢你的帮助?
- They froze my accounts.,- Thank you for your help?
- 这又不是她的错,- 他还没动到我的
- It's not her fault.,- He hasn't gottento mine yet.
我得赶紧把钱取出来,能取多少取多少, 午饭我请客
I'm gonna withdraw and much as I can,as fast as I can.Lunch is on me.
做个刮样检查,看看是不是过敏
Do a scratch test.,Check for allergies.
假如结果是呈阴性,就用广谱抗生素试试
When it comes up negative,,startbroad-spectrum antibiotics.
虚张声势而已,不予理睬, 他们就会失去兴趣
Bullies bully.They don't get a reaction,,they lose interest.
趁我还没来得及把你的头按到马桶里,赶紧照我吩咐的去做
Now go do what I ask before,I stick your heads in toilets.
- 小水獭怎么会在这儿的,- 爸爸昨晚把他领回来的
- How'd otter get here?,- Daddy got him last night.
我拿去干洗了,他们6点关门, 你是怎么领到的?
It was at the dry cleaner.,They close at 6:00.How'd you get it?
我开车到那里
I drove over there.
敲了十来分钟的门,然后求他们
I knockedfor about ten minutes.,And then I begged.
等你好了以后要不要吃点冰淇淋?
How about some ice cream,for when this is through?
- 我肚子疼,- 淡姜酒怎么样?
- My tummy hurts.,- Ginger ale?
好吗?
Yeah?
- 我来照顾她,- 马上回来
- I'll take over.,- Be right back.
他倒是很浪漫的一个人
He's already been really good,at the big romantic gestures,
可一让他洗碗或是准时吃饭或是
but ask him to do the dishesor show up,for a meal on time or
- 开车接送--,- 快好了
- drive her--,- almost done here.
- 你在这儿干什么?,- 我在这儿工作
- What are you doing here?,- I work here.
就这么歇业了,你分明是扮惨相给我看
Passively-aggressively,you gave up your practice.
我还有门诊
I have clinic hours.
现在你又夸张地抹花生酱
Now, you're passively-aggressively,spreading peanut butter
分明是在谴责我,--"看Wilson连吃饭的钱都没了"
with a big sign around your neck saying,,"wilson doesn't have enoughcash for the cafeteria".
知道吗? lenny bruce吸毒死亡之前...,(喜剧明星)
You know, before lenny bruce,died of a drug overdose...
如果你要把滥用毒品的人都摆出来,跟我说教
If you're gonnaconfront me with everyone,who ever abused narcotics,
我得找本书解闷....
I think I'm gonna have to,get something to read....
曾因淫秽语言被逮捕
He was arrestedon obscenity charges.
事情后来变成一连串官司,因为他总是忍不住去招惹警察
He went through a seriesof arrests and trials,because he just couldn'tstop challenging the police.
除了自己那点官司,别的什么都不管
He became obsessed with his own legal problems.
成天用乏味的语言谩骂,警察是法西斯, 侵犯他的权利
And his act turned into long, humorless rants,about fascist cops and the violation of his rights.
知道了知道了, 我晚上不出去乱搞,换成充气娃娃怎么样?
I get it, I get it.I need to change,my nightclub act.You think more props?
House, 刮样分析的结果出来了,过敏源有很多种
House, scratch testis getting results.,A lot of results.
- 她怎么会对每样东西都过敏,- 不可能
- how could she be allergic to everything?,- She can't be.
一定是感染造成的
It has to be an infection.
根据过敏测试阳性结果,判断是感染造成的?
You see a positive allergy test,and decide it's infection?
细菌通过背部的刮痕入侵
The bacteria got into the scratches in her back.
感染是辐射扩散的,形状看起来不象是--
Infections radiate.,That shape of this isn't--
- 吃了它,- 我不饿
- eat this.,- I don't feellike eating.
它会让你感觉好些
It'll make you better.
- 三明治吗?,- 魔法三明治
- A sandwich?,- Magic sandwich.
- 根本就没有这样的--,- 就吃一口怎么样, 小鬼头?
- There's no such thing--,- just take a damn bite,okay, kid?
她居然没对这个有过敏反应,真是太奇怪了
Amazing how she didn't go,into anaphylactic shock.
这根本就不是诊断
That's diagnosticallyridiculous.
是吧, 她对什么都过敏,-- 除了花生酱
Right, she's allergic to,everything except peanuts.
如果真的是过敏,抗生素会导致严重的全身反应
If she is allergic,antibiotics could cause,a massive systemic reaction.
如果真的是过敏, 可她不是
If she's allergic, but she's not.
Chase  你说得没错
Chase, you're right.
外观看起来象是过敏,分析结果也表明是过敏
The shape indicates allergy.,The tests indicate allergy.
对花生酱不过敏,并不意味着他对利多卡因或者--
Just because she's not allergic to peanuts,doesn't mean she's not allergic to lidocane or--
chase  把注射袋挂起来
chase, hang the bag!
明天再来跟我唱反调
You can growa backbone tomorrow.
不, 不能让她用,可导致全身反应的药
No, I'm not givingmy daughter drugs,that could shuther system down.
你知道还有什么能让全身系统关闭吗?,死亡
You know what elseshuts down systems?,Death.
对不起,我不能让你这么做
Sorry.,I can't let you do this.
还好alice hartmann有个讲理的母亲
Luckily,alice hartmann has a mom,who is willingto see reason.
昨天你还说最好是,她父亲来行使监护权
You were in here yesterdaytelling me,her father'sguardianship was best for her.
我还以为今天会换个法官
I honestly figured I'd get,a different judge today.
你现在站在House医生这边了
You agreewith dr. House now.
- 我的孩子真的病了,- 她昨天就已经病了
- Now my kidactually is sick.,- She was sick yesterday.
她的儿科医生不知道问题出在哪里,只说House医生是最棒的
Her pediatrician doesn't know,what's wrong with her,says dr. House is the best.
她失去了监护权,突然之间  House就成了英雄
She loses guardianship.,All of a sudden,house is a hero.
这完全跟我的决定没--
It's got nothing to dowith me deciding--
住口,我听够了
hey, zip it!,I've heard enough.
- 当法官真容易,- 你也给我闭嘴
- This lawyering thingis easy.,- You shut up too.
每个决定都要争来争去,既浪费她的时间, 也浪费我的时间
Arguing over every decision,is a waste of her timeand mine.
既然她的父母意见不一致
Since her parents can'tor won't agree,
我决定把临时监护权叫给一位,以这孩子的健康为重的医生
I'm awarding temporaryguardianship to a doctor,who will place the health of the childabove all else.
我不认为House医生有能力--
I don't think dr. Houseis capable--
- Cuddy医生,- 是的  法官大人
- dr. Cuddy.,- Yes, your honor.
我还没把话说完
No, I was finishingmy sentence.
这孩子交给你了
The kid's all yours.
3点了,把药给我
3:00.,Give me the pills.
我根本不认识这孩子,又怎么能决定什么对她是最有利的
I don't evenknow this kid.,How am I supposed to decidewhat's best for her?
好的  让我来决定
Fine, I'll choose.
我决定站在那位愤怒的医生一边,把药给我
I'm gonna side withthe angry doctor's opinion.,Give me my pills.
我们不该给她用广谱抗菌素
We're not gonna gobroad-spectrum.
万一她真的是过敏
If there's any chancethat she's allergic--
- 根本不可能,- 完全有可能
- there is no chance.,- Of course there's a chance.
- 我求你了,- 不  你不是
- I'm appealing.,- No, you're not.
如果你认为是细菌感染,那就选一种抗生素
If you think it's bacterial,,pick one antibiotic.
一种不够,我们需要的是广谱抗菌素
Not gonna be enough.,We need to gobroad-spectrum.
它能杀死细菌,正是你想要的
It kills bugs.,That's what you want.
给她用甲硝唑
We'll gowith metronidazole.
你不需要出庭指证他违法
you don't have to testifyhe's broken any laws.
虽然我肯定他违法了
Though i'm sureyou could.
只要指证他每天吃多少颗药就行
Just how many pillshe takes in a day.
因为我可以肯定,他没这么多合法处方
Because I'm fairly confidentI can prove that didn't,,uh,have that manylegitimate prescriptions.
我希望没人会因为,我坐在这里跟你说话而送命
I really hope no one dies,while I'm sitting herenot talking to you.
我在trenton警察局的,一个好朋友作了些调查
I--I had a, uh--I had a buddy,at trenton pddo some digging.
你兄弟因为吸毒被抓起来了
Your brother locked upfor drugs.
你的同胞兄弟,连看都不去看望一下
Your own flesh and blood,,and you don't even visit.
而你的老板在药物影响下工作,你却帮着他欺骗警察
But your boss practicesmedicine on drugs,,time to start lyingto the cops.
你罗里罗嗦的到底想要说什么
If I run out for coffee,will I get back,before you make your point?
如果你愿意出庭作证
You, um, you testify...
我保证marcus在两个月内,就可以得到假释
I can make sure that marcus goes free,on parole in less than two months.
我和我兄弟...
My brother and I...
我们在一起长大
we grew upin the same home.
但..  我选了正路
But...,I made something of myself.
他没有
He didn'T.
Foreman医生, 你说这话,好像你从没做过违法的事似的
Dr. Foreman,the way you talk,you'd think,you nevercommitted any crimes yourself.
你和House医生,你们都是冷血的家伙
You and dr. House.,You areboth cold bastards.
你根本不关心你的兄弟,你也不会维护House
You don't give a damn about your brother,,and you can't stand house.
但我劝你接受这个条件,比起这个你更痛恨伪善的人
But I do expect youto take this deal,because you hatehypocrisy more.
House可以选择的有很多,你也曾有两条路
House has had a thousand chances.,You had two chances.
何不给你兄弟一条生路?
Why is your brotherstuck at one?
如果她对对抗生素过敏,我们现在也该看得出了
Well, if she was allergicto this antibiotic,,we would'veseen it by now.
我想我们已经安全度过了过敏时段
I think we areout of the woods,as far as that goeS.
也许他们有时也能对一回
Guess they occasionallyget one right.
你说的倒轻松
You're gonna be glibabout this?
- 你几乎了要她的命,- 我必须做个选择
- You almost killed her.,- I made a choice.
你昨天也做了个决定,难道只有我做决定才叫愚蠢
The same choiceyou made yesterday.,Only when I make it,I'm an imbecile.
你从来就没做过对的事
Every decision you havemade has been wrong.
事情一结束,我就去申请单独监护权
When this over, I'm suing for sole custody.
就因为你不相信医生而我相信他们?
because I trusted doctors when you didn't?
不只是因为前两天发生的事
Because it's not just about the past two days.
只是你最懂什么对Alice最好?,她爱我
Like you have the hotline on,what's best for alice.She loves me.
她和你在一起的时候从来不做家庭作业,从来不梳头发--
She never does her homework when she's with you.,She never brushes her hair--
她心率加快 血压增高,你们两个, 请出去
her heart's racing.Pressure's rising.,The two of you, get out.
我是她的母亲,你不能--
I'm her mother.,You can't just--
你们吵架,导致她的焦虑症发作
you fight.,She has an anxiety attack.
你们两个只会使她更糟,出去别再回来
The two of youare making her worse.,Get out and don't come back.
孩子怎么样了?
How's the kid doing?
比两小时之前好多了,你有钱买午餐?
Much better as ofabout two hours ago.,You got any moneyfor lunch?
如果你管欧芹和碎面包也叫午饭的话
If you likeparsley and croutons.
- Tritter最终也冻结了我的账户,- 真的?
- Tritter finallyfroze my accounts.,- Really?
有什么可吃惊的?,为什么不?
You surprised?,Why wouldn't he?
嗯 我以为他对你特殊对待,一定因为你做过些什么
Well, I figured if he wassingling you out,,you must've donesomething different.
什么 告密?
What, like talking?
是啊 现在他冻结了你的账户,你说不定真会, 你需要现金, 不是吗?
Yeah, and now that he'sfrozen your accounts,,you probably will.You need the cash, right?
他不冻结我的账户, 是我的错,冻结了账户, 还是我的错
He doesn't freezemy accounts, i'm guilty.,He does freezemy accounts, I'm guilty.
Alice在做什么治疗吗?
Is alice havingsome procedure done?
- 她很好, 正在休息,- 在哪?
- She's fine.She's resting.,- Where?
在她的病房,你不应该去--
In her room, where you're,not supposed to--
我刚路过窗户,那儿没人
I was just at the window.,There's no one in there.
她的背包也不在了
Her backpack wasn'tthere either.
你们觉得她父亲有可能--
You don't thinkher father could've--
通知保安
call security.
- 准备推车,- 她身体僵硬 动不了
- Get a gurney.,- she's stiff.She can't move.
我不知道怎么回事,我的意思是, 刚才还挺好
I don't knowwhat happened.,I mean,she seemed fine.
救救她  求求你
Help her, please.
直挺挺的姿势说不定能捞块滑雪橇奖章,(奥运会冰上项目之一要求身体笔直)
On the plus side,she could medal in luge.
肌肉僵化是神经学上的专用术语
Muscle rigidity is almost,exclusively neurological.
幼儿神经轴索性营养不良,她年龄也符合
Neuroaxonal dystrophy.,She's the right age.
除了她的肝功能开始下降
except that her liver's starting to shut down.
- 营养不良不会导致--,- 甲硝唑, 好主意
- No dystrophy would--,- metronidazole.Great idea.
我们不用广谱抗生素,放弃真正能治好她的机会
Let's not go broad-spectrum.,Let's not take any chancesof actually curing her.
- House 你能不能专注于病情?,- 不能! 因为我也被折磨着呢
- House, can you focuson the case?,- No!Because I'm in pain.
就因为你事事都折衷处理
Because you thinkthat compromise,is the answer to everything.
我需要更多的药
I need more pills.
肌肉僵化加上肝脏异常,是Wilson's病(肝豆状核变性)
muscle rigidity plus liver,involvement means wilson'S.
不, 没有角膜环,精神上也没有变化
No, no corneal ring.,No mental changes.
那是什么?
then what?
- 我需要止痛药!,- 不行 要合理剂量--
- I need more pills!,- No, you are ona reasonable--
合理是什么意思?
what the hell does"reasonable" mean?
安静点, 她血压升高了,而且叫也没用--
Keep it quiet.Her B.P.Reacts to stress,,and yelling is not--
如果你认为我不是真疼的话,就别给我药
if you thinkthat I'm not in pain,,then don't give me anything.
连阿司匹林都别给我
Keep me away from the aspirin.
但是我要是真疼的厉害的话,就需要强效的止痛药
But if I'm ina buttload of pain,,I need a buttloadof pills.
很好, 你需要药,可就是不能给你
Fine.You need more pills.,You're not getting them.
阿司匹林的话随你要多少都行
You can have allthe aspirin you want.
我建议大家抽签,输的人驾车去Trenton帮他买白粉
I say we draw straws.Loser drives down,to trenton,scores him an eight-ball.
- 你们谁给她吃过阿司匹林?,- 什么?
- Which one of you twogave her an aspirin?,- What?
症状符合雷亥综合症, 如果用过阿司匹林,(脑病与内脏脂肪变性)
Her symptomsfit reye's syndrome,which doesn't,make any senseunless she took aspirin.
- Rob?,- 没有  她还小
- Rob?,- No way.She's a kid.
我看过那篇
I've read the 800warning labels.
我没有生气,我只想她好起来
I'm not even angry.,I just want her to be okay.
她说谎, 她气得很,因为你拐走了她的孩子
she's lying.She's angry.,Because you kidnappedher kid.
- 要是孩子死了她会气疯,- 我没有
- She'll be angrierif the kid dies.,- I didn'T.
一片阿司匹林加上先前的感染,足以引发现在的症状
One aspirin combinedwith a pre-existing infection,is all it takesto set off an attack.
我没说谎
I'm not lying.
哦 当然 你信誉良好
Well, sure, you've certainly,earned our trust.
Alice入院的前一天晚上在哪里?
Where was alice the night,before she came in?
和我一起,在我家里
With me.,Well, at my house.
我出门了,她和一个临时保姆在一起
I went out.,She stayed with a babysitter.
- 你去哪了?,- 不关你的事
- Where were you?,- None of your business.
你雇佣的那人说不定,给我们的女儿乱服药
You hired someone thatmight've,poisoned our daughter.
她15岁了, 非常负责
She's 15.,She's very responsible.
她是个15岁的药剂师?
Is she a 15-year-old pharmacist?
还是个街上的小孩,需要20块买唇膏或是玩几把扑克?
Or just some kid from down the street,who needed 20 bucksfor lip glossand coupleof tiger beats?
给你那孩子进行血液灌注
Put your kid oncharcoal hemoperfusion.
我们是不是该听听保姆怎么说?
Shouldn't we see whatthe babysitter has to say?
我知道她会怎么说,她会撒谎来保全自己的工作
I know whatshe's gonna say.,She's gonna lieto save her business.
我需要药
I need more pills.
我们要用这台机器去净化你的血液
We are gonna use this machine,to clean your blood.
把你的血液通过一个过滤器,就像鱼池里的渔网一样
It goes out of youand through a filter,like the filterin a fish tank.
实际上挺酷的
It's kind of coolactually.
我害怕
I'm scared.
不会疼的
It won't hurt.
要一段时间会挺无聊的,但不会受伤的
It takes a while, so it'll be boring.,But it won't hurt.
会让你感觉好些
It's gonna makeyou better.
他们怨恨对方, 是吗?,我们再也成不了一家人了
They hate each other,don't they?,We're never gonna betogether again.
哦 这可不一定
Well, you never know.
你还要给我们断水断电吗?
you gonna break out the rubber hoses,,the bright lights?
我可不会为了不想,借钱买午餐去指控House
I'm not gonna testifyjust because,I have toborrow lunch money.
我知道 陷入爱情的女人,什么事情都做的出来
I know.Women don't give up guys,that they'rein love with.
我没爱上House
I'm not in lovewith house.
这家伙精神错乱毫无道德
The guy is unhingedand unethical.
做事从来不为他人着想
Does what he wants with no concern for others.
但是你却支持他
But you stand by him.
- 就不能是忠心和敬重吗?,- 不能
- It can't just beloyalty and respect.,- No.
我是个女的,所以一定是爱上他了?
I'm girl, so i must bein love with him.
不是因为你是女人
Not because you're a girl.
十年前你本可以在微积分上得"A",却自我断送
Because ten years agoyou got an "a",in calculus until you ratted yourself out.
因为你指出老师的错误
Showed your professora mistake he missed.
- 你嫁给了一个--,- 别再说了
- Because you marrieda man--,- don't go there.
你以前是个有原则的人
You used to be someone,who did the right thing.
House改变了你,你觉得这种改变好吗?
House has changed you do you,think it's all beenfor the better?
- 情况如何?,- 闲的无聊
- How's it going?,- Boring.
- 早就告诉你了,- 直到目前为止还好
- Told you.,- So far, so good.
就像5分钟和15分钟之前一样
Just like five minutes ago,,ten minutes before that.
怎么啦?
What's the matter?
她可能发生血栓
She must've thrown a clot.
马上送出去,我通知手术室
Let's get her out of here.,I'll call the O.R.
你说过不疼的!
You said it wouldn't hurt!
- 找到了,- 她体温升高
- Found it.,- She's burning up.
- 给我几秒钟,- Foreman, 她体温高的吓人
- Give me a sec.,- Foreman, she is on fire.
就快到了
Almost there.
- 给我准备降温毯,- 马上
- Get me somecooling blankets now.,- Right away.
每次我们一碰这个孩子,总有事情发生
Every time we touch this kid,,something goes wrong.
归咎于晦气,不是一种诊断
Bad mojo is nota diagnosis.
你干什么非要在我面前炫耀你的藏货
You really had to flashyour private,stashin front of me?
如果我不当着你的面,为我撒谎就容易些?
You find it easierto lie for me,if it's more subtle?
那好
Fine.
你和你的同事说,我冻结了你的账户
Your told your associates thatI had frozen your accounts.
- 是的,- 高明
- Yes.,- Smart lie.
你觉得他们会认为,你被特殊对待是有原因的
You figured they'd thinkthere was a reason,that you'd been singled out.
比如你已经同意指证House
Like that you had agreedto testify against house.
是的, 我假设那就是你这么做的原因
Yeah, I assumethat's why you did it.
你可是有个墙头草的名声在外
You have a reputationas a bitof an opportunist.
在我听说之前你就出卖过自己的上司
You already gave your boss uponce from what I've heard.
为了保住我的工作,他下台我就会丢饭碗
To save my job.,He goes down now,I lose my job.
辞了这份工作你还能找其他的
You lose your job,you fin another one.
你要是被炒得话...
You get fired...
机会可就没那么多了
chances don'tlook so hot.
- 为什么他要炒了我?,- 因为你揭发了他
- Why would he fire to me?,- Because you rolled on him.
- 我没有揭发过他,- 我想你会的
- I haven't rolled on him.,- I think you will.
而且他会认为你已经做了
And he's gonna thinkyou already did.
他所知道的是,我的账户和其他人一样被冻结了
As far as he knows,my accounts are frozen,just like everyone else'S.
24小时之内,你们三人的账户就会解冻
In 24 hours,all three of youwill,have accessto your accounts again.
为什么你要--
Why would you--
知道吗 如果我是个局外人,我会觉得Tritter警官
see, I waslooking at thisas an outsider,,I would sayit was becausedetective tritter had
和Chase医生的这顿饭,吃得很愉快
what appeared to be a very,pleasant lunch with dr. Chase.
不是吗
Yeah.
他们两个看样子在商量什么
The two of themappeared to beworking together.
手术室里的冰袋都哪去了?
How the hell are there,no ice packs in the O.R.?
血栓清除 冰袋支持不了太久,降温毯在哪?
Clot's out.Ice packs aren't going to,hold her for long.Where are the blankets?
在急诊室, 他们正在,处理四车相撞的伤者
In the E.R., They're dealing,with a four-car collision.
我们要在烧坏大脑前,把她的体温降下来
We need to coolthis kid downbefore her brain melts.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
为了稀释血液方便透析,给她用过大量肝素
She got a major doseof heparin,to thin her bloodfor the procedure.
可能导致血小板过低
Could've induced thrombocytopenia.
不太可能,透析已经清除了绝大部分的肝素
That's unlikely.The charcoal,would've absorbeda lot of the heparin.
她以前就贫血,可能是原发性血液疾病
She's been anemic.,Could be a primary blood disorder.
- 或是我们根本就没治愈感染,- 你是说她没有雷亥氏病?
- Or we never curedthe infection.,- Are you saying she never had reye's?
我们才把这个小姑娘置于极度的痛苦中
We just put that little girl,through excruciating pain.
痛苦也不是House的错
The pain wasn't house's fault.
即使血栓是用药的副作用,我们还是能--
Even if the clot wasa reaction,to what we gave herwe still had--
我不需要你来替我掩饰
I don't need you to covermy ass!
我需要的是维柯丁
What I need is my vicodin!
每六个小时才两片,好像给零花钱一样
Two pills every six hours.,Like I'm on an allowance.
她让警察干预医学诊断
She's a given a cop leverage,over medical decisions.
为什么不叫个水管工,问问他的意见?
What the hell?Why don't we get a,plumberin here, ask his opinion?
嘿  Cuddy 你知道牛仔竞技前要称重--
Hey, cuddy, you know any,rodeo clowns who can weigh in--
她人呢?
where the hell is she?
看看她的手臂
Look at her arm.
说了是感染
I told youit was an infection.
- 感染我们已经清除了,- 哦 明显没有
- We fixed the infection.,- Well, apparently not.
我说让你用广谱抗生素,你却把量减到最小
I asked you for broad-spectrum.,You put her onthe bare minimum.
没怀上孩子算是好的,因为你根本不是个好母亲
It's a good thing you failed to,become a mombecause you suck at it.
皮疹给我们提示什么?
What's goodabout this rash?
猜的好, 但是不对
Good guesses, but no.
我们碰都没碰她身上那片皮肤
It's on parts of her body,that we haven't touched.
她烧到103度了,人昏迷又醒了
She's got a feverof 103.,She's in and outof consciousness.
但都不是因为我们的措施
But it's not a reaction,to anything we did.
不是晦气的原因,就是说
Her mojois off the table.,Which means?
哦 就差一点!
Oh, so close!
因为Cuddy的缩手缩脚,现在用广谱抗生素也没用了
Means that thanks to cuddy'scandy-ass approach,broad-spectrum antibioticsare no longer an option.
这个东西又长出了角和獠牙来
This thing has grownhorns and fangs.
我们得弄清楚它的是什么
We gotta figure out what species it is.
用长矛对准它的心脏
Go in with a spearto the heart.
你们心里有怨气
Okay,you guys are sulking.
虽然我不在乎是什么, 但是很明显,不弄清楚的话我没法工作
I don't really care why,but apparently,I can't do my jobwithout finding out.
- Tritter解冻了我们的银行账户,- 可怕, 真是恐怖的消息
- Tritter releasedour bank accounts.,- Horrible,horrible news.
真庆幸还没化脓
Wow, I'm glad we didn't let that fester.
如果是雷亥氏病, 那可能还有水痘病毒,二者经常关联
If she did have reye's,then it could be,varicella.They're associated.
他解冻了我们的财产,你很清楚那意味着什么
He released our money.,You do know what that means.
你应该问,"如果水痘的话, 她为什么不痒呢?"
The correct question is"how could it be varicella,given that she's not itchy"?
- 立克次氏体痘导致皮疹发热和疼痛,- 疼痛 但不会麻痹
- Rickettisal pox causesrash, fever, and muslepain.,- pain, not paralysis.
而落基山斑疹热,正好有皮疹, 发热, 贫血和麻痹
Rocky mountain spotted feveron the other hand.,Rash, fever, anemia, paralysis.
- 而且我对Tritter什么也没说,- 我也没说
- And I didn't sayanything to tritter.,- Neither did I.
或许他就是想让我们以为,其中一个人说过
Maybe he wants us to think,that one of us talked.
- 那奏效了,- 你曾经和他在一起
- It worked.,- You were with him.
- 我们都和他独处过,- 我们可没和他谈笑风生
- We were all with him.,- We weren't laughingwith him.
或许是他放弃了
Maybe he just gave up.
给孩子用氯霉素对付落基山斑疹热
Start the kidon chloramphenicol,for rocky mountainspotted fever.
- 我们能谈谈吗?,- 不行
- Can we talk?,- Nope.
我觉得--
I really think--
要么你指控我, 想让我原谅你,或者你没有, 于是来讨要奖赏
either you screwed meand you want absolution,,or you didn'tand you want applause.
两个我都不感兴趣
Either wayI'm not interested.
忙着呢
Busy.
- 你还好吧?,- 是 当然
- You okay?,- Yeah, sure.
当我问 "你还好吗",我是问House做了什么?
What I meant by"are you okay"?,Is what the helldid house do?
- 没什么,- 他说什么了?
- Nothing.,- What did he say?
House的那副粗鲁嘴脸我见得多了,通常都是为了达到某些目的
I've seen house be rudea thousand times,,usually to achieve something.
我从未听过他无目的的讲那些话
I have never seen himbe mean just because he can.
真的?
Seriously?
- 他说什么了?,- 没什么 无关紧要
- What did he say?,- Nothing.Doesn't matter.
哦 House对你的口气我也见得多了,但是他从来伤不到你
Well, I've seen house be rudeto you a thousand times,,but I've never seen itget to you.
人们觉得House只是口无遮拦
People think house hasno inner censor.
实际上他只是没发作,当他想伤害别人
But the fact is he holds himself back,,because when he wants to hurt,
他很清楚别人的软肋在哪
he knows just whereto poke a sharp stick.
我一直想要个孩子,House也知道
I have been tryingto get pregnant,and house knew.
他说我会是个失败的母亲
He told me I wouldfail as a mother.
你这么伤心难道认为他说的对?
And you're this upset,because you think he's right?
我已经三次植入胚胎了
I've had three separateimplantations.
前两次没着床,后一个没保住
The first twonever took.,The last one I lost.
我很遗憾 那不是你的错,这些只是生理现象
I'm sorry.You didn't fail.,Those wherephysical events.
小女孩疼痛害怕的时候
A little girl is...,scared and in pain.
我不知该怎么办,只想着不犯错
I was awkward, terrified,of doing the wrong thing.
那很正常,那--
That's normal.,That's--
我没拥抱她
I didn't hug her.
她的小手也没牵一下
I didn't even reach outand hold her hand.
只是告诉她没事的
I told her it wasgonna be okay.
她需要你的安慰
She needed reassurance.
我还说她父母会可能会和好
I told her her folks,might get back together.
当我看见别人和孩子在一起时,一切都是那么自然
When I see people with their kids,,it's so natural.
就像他们的基因里有个,儿童相处说明书一样
It's like they havean instruction book,imprinted on their genes.
或许我的基因就是缺少这点
Maybe I just didn'tget a copy.
或许我成为一个母亲的难度,就像五音不全的人去唱歌剧
Maybe my wanting to be a motheris like,a tone deaf personwanting to sing opera
- 或是瘫痪的想--,- 喔喔喔
- or a paraplegicwho wants to--,- whoa, whoa, whoa.
我体会到你说的,"House找准你软肋"的意思了
Well, I see what you meanabout house,pokingin the right spot.
氯霉素不起作用
Chloramphenicolisn't working.
- 用了多大剂量?,- 是啊, 怀疑Chase搞砸了
- What dosedid you give her?,- Yeah, maybe chasescrewed up.
最后总要怀疑到我,我只是帮你们快点到这一步
We always end up there.,Just getting a jump on it.
我把药量加倍了
I doubled her up.
病菌变异了
The infection's morphed.
- 转移到了肌鞘,- 坏死性筋膜炎?
- It's moved intoher muscle sheath.,- Necrotizing faciitis?
药物不能渗透
That's impervious to drugs.
唯一的治疗方法...,就是切除坏死的组织
The only treatment...,is to cut awaythe infected area.
- 只能截肢,- 手臂和腿?
- So we amputate.,- Arm and leg?
没有准确的诊断,我们不能把一个六岁孩子切成两半
We can't cut a six-year-old kid in half,without a confirmeddiagnosis.
感染太快而且我们又浪费了太久,没时间做细菌培养了
Moves too quicklyand we waited too long.,We don't have timefor a culture.
我们至少再观察她几个小时,确定是否会扩散
We can at least observe herfor a few hours.,Confirm the rashis spreading.
一旦扩散 她就死定了
It spreads, she dies.
说的是把她变成瘸子
You're talking about crippling her.
甚至还没确定是感染
We're not even certainthis was an infection.
是啊! 她才六岁! 她可爱!,所以不可能被病菌蚕食!
Right!She's six!She's cute!,She can't haveflesh-eating bacteria!
肯定不可能!,我们阳光和宠物去治她好了
It's just wrong!,Let's cure her with sunshine and puppies.
可爱的孩子病死了,无辜的医生坐监牢
Cute kids die of illnesses.,Innocent doctors go to jail.
因为你们这些懦弱的人,不敢站出来承担责任
And it because cowardslike you,won't stand up and do what's required.
就会坐在这抱怨谁更可怜
You can sit around and moan,about who's the bigger weakling.
我得工作去了
I'm gonna go do my job.
那该是怎样的生活,要是她失去--
what kind of quality of life,will she have without--
只有活着
great thing about life.
才谈得上质量
It's got qualities.
如果我们不同意呢?
and if we can't agree?
我不知道
I don't know.
他以前也这么发飚过
He's yelled at us before.
是因为他觉得我们的想法不对,而不是怀疑我们出卖他
because he thoughtour theories were dumb.,Not because our theories were sending him to jail.
他正在药瘾戒除期,行为会轻微偏执
He's goingthrough withdrawal.,Could be causing mild paranoia.
总会有这个过程,我们也得跟着忍受
It'll pass, we justhave to suffer thought.
我们从来没排除过敏症
We never ruled out allergy.
我们给她用药,她也没出现副作用
We gave her drugs.,She had no negative reaction.
我们给她腹部手术,她的腹部就出现皮疹
We cut open her belly.,She got a rash on her belly.
我们在她后背做过敏性测试,她的后背就出现皮疹
We did a scratch teston her back.,She got a rash on her back.
我知道House排除了晦气因素,但这决不可能是巧合
I know house ruled out mojo,,but it can't be a coincidence--
玩猜诊断的游戏太晚了,不是吗?
too late to be playing,differential games, isn't it?
把那东西拿开,我可不想被灼伤
Get that thing away from me.,I don't want to get burned.
激光笔不会灼伤你的 天才
Laser pointersdon't burn you, genius.
皮肤当然不会,视网膜会
Skin, no.,Retina, yes.
你不信我的准确度?
You don't trust my aim?
或许你该把所有怕光的都遮住--
Maybe you should cover any sensitive--
他那通小狗的说辞有问题
he was wrongabout the puppies.
House, 你得终止手术
House, you gottastop the surgery.
- 她不是坏死性筋膜炎,- 噢 太好了
- She doesn't havenecrotizing faciitis.,- Oh, good.
她得了红细胞生成性原卟啉症,对光过敏
She's got erythropoieticprotoporphyria.,She's allergic to light.
这是遗传性的,父母任何一方携带即可
It's genetic, either parentcould've carried it.
我知道那是什么,感染症状更符合
I know what it is.,Infection fits better.
每次她暴露在手术灯下,病情就会更严重
She gets worse every time,she goes under surgical lights.
- 爸爸带她外出--,- 肝脏也衰竭了
- Dad takes her outside--,- liver's shot too.
- 难道她吞了手电筒?,- 停止手术
- She swallow a flashlight?,- Stop the surgery.
- 别挡我的路,- 不行! 我
- Get the hellout of my way.,- No, I'm--unh!
光线破坏了血细胞
Light damagesthe blood cells.
被破坏的血细胞里含有原卟啉
The damaged blood cells contain protoporphyrin.
原卟啉在肝脏富集
The protoporphyrinbuilds up in the liver.
这就是肝功能衰竭的原因
That's why the liver'sshutting down.
停下
Stop.
她怎么可能对光线过敏?,之前从没有这个问题
how can she be allergic to light?,She's never had thisproblem before.
过敏反应一出生就有了
The negative reactionstarts at birth.
随年龄的增长逐渐严重
It reaches critical massaround this age.
她的血细胞里产生些化学物质,在光照下会发生反应
Her blood cellscreate chemicals,in reaction to light.
当血液流经肝脏时,受损的细胞被过滤出来
When they reach the liver,,it tries to filter outthe bad cells.
释放的化学物质损害了肝脏,结果导致结石
The chemicals damagethe liver,,and one byproductis gallstones.
她的情况会越来越糟吗?
So she'll just keepgetting worse?
光过敏症是可控制的,我们给她β-胡萝卜素
Ep can be managed.,We'll give herbeta-carotene.
她需要用特制光源,窗户需要光线过滤装置
She's gonna needspecial light bulbs,and filterson the windows.
她大概只能在家里上学了
She's probably gonnaneed to be home schooled.
她的生活会有很多不便,但她能活下去
Her life will becomplicated,but she will live.
怎么会得上这病的?
How do you getsomething like this?
- 是遗传性的,- 那我们之一....
It's genetic.,So one of us...
必须双方都是携带者
both of youmust be carriers.
她醒来会想见你们  所以..
She's gonna want to see you,when she wakes up.So...
别再吵了
don't screw it up.
有什么新消息?
So, what's new?
- House误诊了,- 以前也有过
- House missed one.,- That's happened before.
他差点使小女孩残废,我及时纠正
He nearly maimeda little girl.,I got it right.
我还告诉他,算了不重要
And I told him,and it didn't matter.
Chase 你拯救了一个病人,这是你最大的奖赏
Chase, you solved one.You helped a patient.,That better beenough for you.
*贝克特的话剧本来叫"等待House的赞同",后来觉得这那么叫太沮丧了
Beckett was gonna call his play"waiting for,house's approval"but decidedit was too grim.
相信我,我不会再等下去了
Trust me.,I'm not waiting anymore.
我需要30块银币,(犹大出卖耶稣的价格)
I'm gonna need30 pieces of silver.